{"data":[{"question":"She went to meet him with an air of ________.","a":"expectant","b":"expectancy","c":"expect","d":"expectation","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Preposition (by, of, in, on...) + Verb_ing\/noun\/noun phrase (adj + noun).\u00a0\n- Expectancy: the feeling that something pleasant or exciting is going to happen.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Alexander Graham Bell ________ the telephone by the time I was born.","a":"had already invented","b":"has already finished","c":"already finished","d":"already finish","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (by the time I was born).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The army ________ the enemy's capital.","a":"occupied (v)","b":"occupied (adj)","c":"occupation","d":"occupational","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"People objected ________ to wait so long.","a":"with having","b":"to having","c":"for having","d":"about having","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Object to doing sth: to feel or say that you oppose or disapprove of something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Is April twenty-first the day ________? - No, the twenty-second.","a":"you'll arrive then","b":"when you arrive","c":"on that you'll arrive","d":"when you'll arrive on","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When: relative pronoun for time.\u00a0\n.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The severe drought ________ occurred last summer ruined the corn crop.","a":"that is","b":"which it","c":"it","d":"that","answer":"4","explain":"\n- That(pronoun): used as the subject in the defining relative clause","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Florida, ________ the Sunshine State, attracts many tourists every year.","a":"is","b":"known as","c":"is known as","d":"that is known as","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use past participle to shorten the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The new shopping mall is gigantic. It's advertised as a place ________ you can find just about anything you might want to buy.","a":"where","b":"which","c":"in where","d":"in that","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Where: relative pronoun for place.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Lola's marriage has been arranged by her family. She is marrying to a man ________","a":"that she hardly knows him","b":"whom she hardly knows","c":"whose she hardly knows","d":"she hardly knows him","answer":"2","explain":"- We use whom + Clause as the relative clause","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"People who exercise frequently have greater physical endurance than those ________.","a":"who doesn't","b":"that doesn't","c":"which don't","d":"who don't","answer":"4","explain":"\n- who don't= PEOPLE Who don't exercise.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}